At 30,000 feet. There's Nowhere to Run.
Flight 7500 is a thriller, horror, mystery film directed by Takashi Shimizu.
Flight 7500 departs Los Angeles International Airport bound for Tokyo.
As the overnight flight makes its way over the Pacific Ocean during its ten-hour course, the
passengers encounter what appears to be a supernatural force in the cabin.
Laura Baxter, played by Leslie Bibb.
Suzy Lee, played by Jamie Chung.
Rick, played by Jerry Ferrara.
Brad Martin, played by Ryan Kwanten.
Pia Martin, played by Amy Smart.
Jacinta Bloch, played by Scout Taylor-Compton.
Flight 7500 is a 2014 American supernatural horror film directed by Takashi Shimizu
and starring Leslie Bibb, Jerry Ferrara, Ryan Kwanten, and Amy Smart.
It tells the story of a supernatural force on a commercial airline flight.
The film was released in the United States on April 12, 2016, by CBS Films
and Lionsgate, after being released theatrically in Asia.
The film explores themes of supernatural, flight, ghost, pacific  ocean, brisk.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.